<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>issues on David Trumbell</title>
    <link>https://djtrumbe.github.io/tags/issues/</link>
    <description>Recent content in issues on David Trumbell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 10:14:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://djtrumbe.github.io/tags/issues/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Drobo: Thin Provisioning</title>
      <link>https://djtrumbe.github.io/2010/03/04/drobo-thin-provisioning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 10:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://djtrumbe.github.io/2010/03/04/drobo-thin-provisioning/</guid>
      <description>If you know me, you know that I&amp;#8217;m a huge proponent of Drobo. As of late, the frustration level with Drobo is increasing and it may have edged away at this enthusiasm.
My most recent frustration came when I upgraded a drive in my Drobo to increase the usable space to more then 2TB. After the Drobo finished updating all of its partitions, I was left with a partition that was labeled &amp;#8216;unallocated&amp;#8217; in the Drobo dashboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O2 Data Frequently Drops</title>
      <link>https://djtrumbe.github.io/2009/09/15/o2-data-frequently-drops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2009 12:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://djtrumbe.github.io/2009/09/15/o2-data-frequently-drops/</guid>
      <description>I know that much has been made of data and connectivity problems on AT&amp;amp;T in the States, but I&amp;rsquo;ve found O2 to be just as bad, if not worse. About once per day, even though I have full bars and am connected to 3G, my iPhone is unable to receive any data. Loading webpages doesn&amp;rsquo;t work, refreshing mail doesn&amp;rsquo;t work, connecting to the App Store doesn&amp;rsquo;t work, etc. This occurs for about 5 to 10 minutes at a time and can sometimes occur multiple times per day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Hardware Problems</title>
      <link>https://djtrumbe.github.io/2009/07/08/apple-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2009 19:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://djtrumbe.github.io/2009/07/08/apple-problems/</guid>
      <description>Apple products have not been kind to me over the past couple of months.
For starters, about 2 months ago, the plastic on my iPhone&amp;rsquo;s back cracked right at the mute switch. This is a common problem that has been documented all over the internet (link1, link2). Here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of mine: Soon after this happened, I purchased a second battery from the Apple store. Good thing I did, because the very next day, my original battery wouldn&amp;rsquo;t charge.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>