<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on David Trumbell</title>
    <link>https://djtrumbe.github.io/tags/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on David Trumbell</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 10:14:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://djtrumbe.github.io/tags/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Drobo: Thin Provisioning</title>
      <link>https://djtrumbe.github.io/2010/03/04/drobo-thin-provisioning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2010 10:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://djtrumbe.github.io/2010/03/04/drobo-thin-provisioning/</guid>
      <description>If you know me, you know that I&amp;rsquo;m a huge proponent of Drobo. As of late, the frustration level with Drobo is increasing and it may have edged away at this enthusiasm.
My most recent frustration came when I upgraded a drive in my Drobo to increase the usable space to more then 2TB. After the Drobo finished updating all of its partitions, I was left with a partition that was labeled &amp;lsquo;unallocated&amp;rsquo; in the Drobo dashboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Browsing the web is for saps.</title>
      <link>https://djtrumbe.github.io/2009/09/07/browsing-the-web-is-for-saps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2009 11:11:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://djtrumbe.github.io/2009/09/07/browsing-the-web-is-for-saps/</guid>
      <description>Do you have a specific set of webpages that you browse to every day?
I do. I used to have all of these sites bookmarked and placed into specific news folders in Firefox or Safari. Right-clicking on a folder would present the option to &amp;lsquo;Open All in Tabs&amp;rsquo; and all of my favorites would be right there for me to filter through. This was easy to setup and I had all of my regular pages a couple of clicks away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Security Threat</title>
      <link>https://djtrumbe.github.io/2009/09/06/wordpress-security-threat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2009 14:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://djtrumbe.github.io/2009/09/06/wordpress-security-threat/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been posted all over the internet as of late, but I&amp;rsquo;d like to remind everyone of the security threat to WordPress blogs:
WordPress 2.8.4: Security Release
How to Keep WordPress Secure
From the above links, the way to keep yourself safe from this attack is by upgrading. Make sure you back your DB beforehand. The easiest way to backup your DB is via this plugin:
wp-db-backup
The sooner you upgrade, the sooner you are safe from this exploit.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>